ing.com 2010-11-22

# Privacy statement - ING

ING Groep N.V. (hereinafter referred to as 'ING') will do its best to ensure that the processing of your personal data is carried out in such a way that your privacy is protected and safeguarded as much as possible. ING collects your personal data only to the extent that it is necessary to provide you with our services, for the development of web statistics reports, web surfing analysis solely regarding the ING.com website, and to comply with mandatory requirements.

ING collects and stores the following visitor information regarding the usage of this website: date and time of day you access our website, time zone, screen resolution, browser type, browser language, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, number of hits, the pages visited, previous/subsequent sites visited, length of user session and anonymous aggregate reports regarding visitor interactions that may include for example: aggregate reports of clicking or mouse activity, aggregate reports of scrolling activity and recreation of visitor browsing sessions solely regarding the ING.com website.

ING does not collect any unique information or any personal data about you (such as your name, e-mail address or other contact information) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. ING does not collect any information about other websites you visit, programs you run on your computer, passwords you use or any other key strokes in fields that have been qualified as sensitive by the webmaster of such sites.

The information mentioned above is gathered by using a cookie. A cookie is a small line of text that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually alter the setting of your browser to prevent that. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please refer to the "help" file of your Internet browser to learn how to either block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.

This Privacy Statement may be modified from time to time to comply with applicable laws, or to reflect our updated business practises, without prior notice. Please check this page periodically for any changes that may be posted.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or our data processing activities, please

contact us via this website.
